


<table>

<tbody><tr>








<th align="left" width="75">

Time

</th>

<th align="left">

Room

</th>

<th align="left">

Panel

</th>

</tr>




    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>Creators</td><td valign="top"><strong>Guests of Honor Photocall</strong><br/>CVG Guests of Honor Photography Session, not open to con-goers.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong>, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, <strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, <strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, Perrin Klumpp, <strong>Harry Knowles</strong>, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, <strong>John Kovalic</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong>, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, <strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, Video Team, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong>, Peter Verrant, <strong>David Weber</strong>, <strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>How to Play Matrix Tag</strong><br/>Do
you have what it takes to help Neo win the war for Zion ? Or will you
support Agent Smith in his quest to subjugate the humans? In Matrix
Tag, two teams vie for power over the fate of the human race. Players
choose the roles of Agent Smith, Neo, Morpheus, Trinity, Agent and
Zionist. Any number of people can play, joining in and leaving at any
time. Players are free to attend other programming during the
Convention, as they seek out Agents and Zionists and gain strength for
their team.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Futuretech, Comic Style</strong><br/>How are future technologies depicted in comics, manga and animation?  Let's talk about spacecraft propulsion  
systems, computing, robotics, off-world habitats, AI, and other  related subjects.<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Buth, Seth Eden, Ben Huset, Jonathan Palmer, Anna Waltz</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>CONvergence 101:  Surviving a Four-Day Weekend</strong><br/>As
we head into our tenth year with a bonus extra day, this panel is a
must for new attendees. Come and learn where and when the cool stuff is
and how to get the most from your weekend at CONvergence!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Jay Curry, Michael Lee, Jen Manna</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>City as Character</strong><br/>New
Crobuzon, Gotham City, The Sprawl, Newford, even Minneapolis in War for
the Oaks. What authors use their cities in the most interesting ways?
How does the city contribute to the story?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Paula Fleming, Cabell Gathman, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Philip Kaveny, John Shea, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Return of The Satellite of Love?</strong><br/>With
so many Mystery Science Theatre 3000 related off-shoots out there
(RiffTrax, The Film Crew, Cinematic Titanic), it can be hard to follow
the latest developments. Come discuss your favorite new ventures and
riffs.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Nick Larson, Steven Manfred, David Margosian</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>How to Play the Steam Century Mystery LARP</strong><br/>The
Steam Century Mystery LARP is a multifaceted game that combines
elements of live action roleplaying and crime dramas. Players follow a
trail of clues by investigating rooms, speaking to costumed characters
and playing games of skill. Players sign up at game registration and
attend a 30 minute orientation which explains the world of Steam
Century and how to interact with props and characters.
Game play takes place over a set period of time, but is designed to be
played intermittently. Players are encouraged to take part in other con
activities during the game. Characters and clues can be found
throughout the con.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>D&amp;D: 4th Edition</strong><br/>How is the 4th edition of Dungeons and Dragons holding up?  Metal detectors will be provided at the door for your protection.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jeff Hagen, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Rob Johnson, Troy Small</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Spectacular Spiderman</strong><br/>Discuss this new animated take on an old classic superhero and meet the executive producer of the series.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Otaku: Your Wacky Anime Neighbors</strong><br/>Are
you wondering what Anime is all about? Curious whether there is any
difference between a cos-play and a masquerade? Want to learn about
Anime Conventions? Then this is the panel for you.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jessi Silver, Jo Thomsen, Matt Weinberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Emergent Genres And Movements</strong><br/>A discussion of The New Weird, Mundane Science Fiction, Space-Westerns, and other current movements in the field.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rob Callahan, Matthew Lee Davis, Damian Sheridan, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Ecology of Monsters</strong><br/>Hypothesize
about how an ecological system would fare if the world were overrun by
zombies, monsters, and other creatures of the night.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Melissa Kaercher, Taylor Kent, Chris Pasquarette, Ellie Younger</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Fanzines Invented the Internet</strong><br/>Everything
anyone does online today was basically invented by fans in zines and
apas well before most people even had even heard of a personal
computer. We'll also look at some zines from 1999 and illustrate how
things have changed since then.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Holly Day, David Emerson, Scott K. Jamison, Greg Prickman, David E. Romm, Joan Marie Verba</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>1.18.08: Marketing of a Film</strong><br/>Let's
look back at some of the best and worst marketing campaigns in the
history of the film industry. Share your ideas for future film
marketing.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, Troy LaFaye, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doctor Who by Decade: The Sixties</strong><br/>Covering
the 1960's era Dr. Who, this is the first in a series of four panels
exploring the rich and varied history of the classic British
science-fiction series, focusing on the Hartnell and Troughton eras.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Ellis, Steven Manfred, Charlie Paulsen, Michael Scott Shappe, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Where Do You Start?</strong><br/>What is the initial genesis or kernel idea of a book?  Do you start with a character?  A world?  A cool scene?  A plot?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joel Arnold, Dana M. Baird, Garnet Gyre, Michael Merriam, Doug Texter</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing John &amp; Peter</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>John Kovalic</strong>, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 6:00pm - 7:00pm</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Mark Time Awards</strong><br/>Mark
Time Awards, starts at 6 PM?. The Mark Time Award is given each year to
honor the Best Science Fiction Audio Production on the Planet. And the
Ogle Award for Best Fantasy Audio Production of the Year.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Windy Bowlsby, Jerry Stearns, Tim Wick, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 7:00pm - 8:00pm</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Opening Ceremonies</strong><br/>Opening Ceremonies<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong>, Windy Bowlsby, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, <strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Christopher Jones, <strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, Perrin Klumpp, <strong>Harry Knowles</strong>, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, <strong>John Kovalic</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong>, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, <strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, Jeremy Stomberg, Video Team, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong>, <strong>David Weber</strong>, <strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, Pat Wick, Tim Wick, Ishmael Williams, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Build Your Own Monster</strong><br/>Develop, design, and build your own terrifying monster out of various supplies.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Terry Faust</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Video Game Blogs and Podcasts</strong><br/>There
are so many video game blogs and podcasts out there, including Kotaku,
Joystiq, 1-Up, Retronauts, and many others. What are your favorites for
gaming news and which are some to avoid?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matt Everhart, Tara Nelson, Tim Wilsie</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Censorship in Comics - The Past and Future</strong><br/>The
landscape has changed drastically since the Comics Code Authority was
established in 1954. Most publishers don't even submit for CCA approval
anymore. How has this impacted the way stories are told and what part
did the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund play in the matter?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Britt Aamodt, Terry Beatty, <strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, Damian Sheridan, Video Team, Tim Uren, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Closet Geeks... Come Out, Come Out Wherever You Are!</strong><br/>When
did you realized you were a geek? Are you considering stepping out of
the geek closet? If you told people you were going to be 'out of town
this weekend,' then this panel is for you!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Beitscher, Rob Callahan, Paul Harmeyer, Sarah Hertz, Taylor Kent, Pete Lane</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>6 Impossible Things Before Breakfast</strong><br/>Highly
improbable, unlikely and "You Must Be Joking!" usage of swords,
firearms and other weaponry in science fiction and fantasy. Let's talk
about the best and the worst.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Catherine Lundoff, Rebecca Marjesdatter</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Dream Cast</strong><br/>No,
this isn't about the Sega video game console. If you could sit in the
casting chair, who would you cast in upcoming movies and why? If you
could rewind the clock, who would you re-cast?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ed Eastman, David Margosian</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Star Trek: The New Voyages and Beyond</strong><br/>Star
Trek is back in the hands of its fans again. Let's discuss the
direction the fans are taking this beloved property. Some productions
even include members of the original casts.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Steve Erickson, Rob Johnson, George Richard, Gordon Smuder</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 8:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Krushenko's Silver Edition Party</strong><br/>Krushenko's
opened at Minicon 1983. Come and celebrate the past, present, and
future of this speculative fiction salon. Party runs until midnight.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Matrix Tag (All Ages)</strong><br/>Do
you have what it takes to help Neo win the war for Zion ? Or will you
support Agent Smith in his quest to subjugate the humans? In Matrix
Tag, two teams vie for power over the fate of the human race. Players
choose the roles of Agent Smith, Neo, Morpheus, Trinity, Agent and
Zionist. Any number of people can play, joining in and leaving at any
time. Players are free to attend other programming during the
Convention, as they seek out Agents and Zionists and gain strength for
their team.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Not all Munchkins Live in Oz</strong><br/>Collectable
Card Games are still going strong and there's more CCG's out there
besides Magic: The Gathering and Pokemon. What are some of your
favorites and which ones should you leave on the shelves?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matthew Lee Davis, Nate French, Pete Lane, Morgan Stana, Bob Wagner</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Songwriting and Filking</strong><br/>In
addition to her numerous novels, Mercedes Lackey is an accomplished
song-writer. Come and learn about her abilities in music composition as
well as the local filking scene.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Justin Hartley, Beth Kinderman, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, Amanda Newman, Laramie Sasseville, Dave Stagner</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Smackdown Panel</strong><br/>Cereal
Mascot Smackdown - Many will enter but only one will win. Watch out for
that Captain Crunch - he's sneaky and vicious and cuts the roof of your
mouth!<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, Kelvin Hatle, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Christopher Jones, Melissa Kaercher, Joe Scrimshaw, Video Team, Tim Uren, Tim Wick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>GLBT SF&amp;F that Everyone Should Read</strong><br/>For
over six years, the North Country Gaylaxians have been meeting monthly
to discuss SF&amp;F books with GLBT connections. In that time we have
come across books that we would not recommend and those we think are
gems. In this panel, we will discuss those books that we have found to
be especially good and would recommend to all audiences.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joe Agee, Bob Alberti, Andrew Berthke, Don Kaiser, Claudia Slovacek, Jason Tucker</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>History of Local Twin Cities Fandom</strong><br/>While
this may be CONvergence's 10th anniversary, the history of local fandom
extends much further back. Come with us as we see just how deep the
rabbit hole goes.<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Emerson, Virginia Jensen, Philip Kaveny, David E. Romm, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>What are the Most Influential Sci-Fi Films of All Time?</strong><br/>2001,
Star Wars, Star Trek: The Motion Picture, Independence Day, Blade
Runner, The Day the Earth Stood Still, Forbidden Planet, Close
Encounters of the Third Kind, The Black Hole, Tron, Terminator, Alien,
Battle Beyond the Stars, and others. You decide.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, Rob Johnson, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, Chuck Waibel, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Supernatural: The Panel</strong><br/>Are
you a fan of Supernatural? Do you call it the "Dean Show?" Why do you
watch Supernatural and why should the rest of us give it a chance?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Holly Johnson, Mara Kapp, Teresa Kramer, Jo Thomsen, Matt Weinberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Evening Reading with Larry</strong><br/>Join Larry Dixon for an intimate reading in the Dorian Gray Memorial Literary Lounge<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Larry Dixon</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Design Workshop</strong><br/>Andrew
Probert has served as a production designer for Star Trek, Battlestar
Galactica and Airwolf. Learn about how designs take shape in this
interactive workshop.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Andrew Probert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Loving the Loathing</strong><br/>Do you play Kingdom of Loathing online?  If not, you are missing out.  Grab some meat and join us!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Tamyra DeWandeler, Melissa Kaercher, Jen Manna, David E. Romm</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Match Game '08</strong><br/>Following the Smackdown panel, join a crazy group as we recreate this 1970's classic gameshow.  Panel starts at 11:30 PM.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Crist Ballas, Kelvin Hatle, Charles Hubbell, Melissa Anne Murphy, Jen Scott, Joe Scrimshaw, Gordon Smuder, Jeremy Stomberg, <strong>Len Wein</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Slash-Fiction</strong><br/>From
it's humble beginnings in photocopied 'zines to the explosion of the
Internet Age, this is your place to discuss all things "slash"
(typically male/male and female/female trysts or relationships). What's
good, what's bad, and what's OMGz?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Garnet Gyre, Revolutionary Jo, Mara Kapp, Rebecca Marjesdatter, Black Squirrel</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Backyard Astronomy</strong><br/>What
are some great places to stargaze near the Twin Cities that are
isolated enough to avoid light pollution? If you are a budding
astronomer, what sort of equipment should you invest in? If the sky is
clear, we may head outside for a quick celestial overview at the end of
the panel.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Huset, Rachel Kronick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Band Geeks!</strong><br/>Did
you play an instrument in middle school or high school? Do you still
play today? If you have kids, do you encourage musical instrument use
for them? Come and share your band geek memories!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joel Arnold, David Emerson, Marie Hulslander, Katie Nelson, Tracie Peters</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Fantasy in Chinese Martial Arts Films</strong><br/>Join
Jose' Figueroa as he reviews how the Wuxia style of martial arts has
grown in Hong Kong Cinema over the years and became Hollywood
mainstream thanks to director's like Ang Lee. Wuxia can best be
described as chivalric fiction mixed with Chinese swords, sorcery, and
martial arts. Come and learn more about this exciting genre of film!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jose' Figueroa</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Paranormal Investigation as TV Journalism</strong><br/>Ghost
Hunters, Most Haunted, and two different UFO Hunters have graced our
screens in the last few years. What is the continued popularity of
these shows and are there any areas of the paranormal that haven't been
tapped for an investigative series? Are there any local hot-spots to
check out?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Michael Beitscher, Pete Lane</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Thu 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Thursday Night Bedtime Stories with the 'Pods</strong><br/>Escape
Pod, Pseudo Pod, and Pod Castle ... three weekly audio casts from the
Escape Artists! Come and listen to a bed-time story with some of the
latest and greatest of these audio giants of Science Fiction, Horror,
and Fantasy! Join us on the 22nd floor in 2201 for back-to-back stories
of speculation, fantasy, and fun. Wear your fluffy bunny slippers and
bathrobe, if you like ... just come prepared to listen to some really
great tales of modern SF!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Rust</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Flip-Book Animation</strong><br/>Learn the basics of 2-D animation by creating your own flip book.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matt Waterhouse</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Casual vs. Hardcore</strong><br/>Are
you a casual gamer that loves Wii Sports? Or a Hardcore gamer who loves
Bioshock and Gears of War? Are the two groups mutually exclusive or is
there room for some overlap? Can someone transition from one group to
the other?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matt Everhart, Nessa Fedde, Jen Manna, Matt Savelkoul, Jeremy Stomberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>History of Manga</strong><br/>Learn
about the history of Japanese comic books and how they continue to
influence Western comics and other varieties of entertainment today.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Melissa Erdman, Melissa Gregory, Scott K. Jamison</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>The "Geek" as an Ensemble Character</strong><br/>Wesley.
Hiro. Chuck. Hurley. Willow. They are all geeks. Is it now a staple of
ensemble series, books, or movies to include a geek or nerd character?
How do we feel about this increased representation? What is
stereotypical and what do the writers get right?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eve Cain, Cabell Gathman, Marguerite Krause, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Influence of Joseph Campbell</strong><br/>The
mythological story structure of Joseph Campbell has influenced science
fiction and fantasy writing. His book, "The Hero with a Thousand Faces"
and his Bill Moyers video series have revolutionized our knowledge of
the mythological story structure. Come and share your observations!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dana M. Baird, David Emerson, Garnet Gyre, John Shea, Chuck Waibel</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Growing Up Geek</strong><br/>What
is it like growing up as a geek? Is there a greater acceptance of geek
and nerd culture nowadays? (teen and tween panelists encouraged)<br/><font size="-1"><em>Tabitha Anderson, Mariah Fryer, Pete Lane, Joan Marquez, Alyssia Rayl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Thunderbirds are Go!</strong><br/>Granada
Ventures has authorized a new Thunderbirds series. Come celebrate the
classic supermarionation series and learn about what's in store for our
heroes.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ed Eastman, Joan Marie Verba</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Morning Reading with Mercedes</strong><br/>Join Mercedes Lackey for an intimate reading in the Dorian Gray Memorial Literary Lounge<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Mechanics of an Image 101: Why Does It Work</strong><br/>There are many images in science-fiction and fantasy that are called  
"iconic" because they are so striking when they are seen for the  
first time.  Why does this happen?  How are elements of the image  
(such as color, line quality, and gesture) used to create a striking  
effect?  Who are the mystery people behind your favorite posters,  
book covers, and gaming art, and why are their images so great?   
Artists and art appreciators alike are welcome to the discussion.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, Melissa Kaercher, Philip Kaveny, Chris Pasquarette</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Facepainting and Hairbraiding</strong><br/>Get something fun and geeky on your face while getting your hair braided.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Melissa Kaercher, Jim Shields, Laine Worth</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Homophobia and Racism in Online Gaming</strong><br/>It's
sad but true - there are many bigots hiding behind the anonymity of a
screen-name out there on services like World of Warcraft and X-Box
Live. What do you do when you hear offensive remarks and what steps can
you take to avoid and report instances when you hear them? On the
flip-side, are people overreacting or assuming things?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Becca Armstrong, Cabell Gathman, Paul Harmeyer, Colleen Palmer</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Titan Tower under Crisis!</strong><br/>Marv
Wolfman created the New Teen Titans and spearheaded the DC epic Crisis
on Infinite Earths (the aftershocks of which are still being felt
nearly 25 years later). Join him for an informative Q&amp;A.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Marv Wolfman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Secret Origins of CONvergence</strong><br/>How
did CONvergence come about? Whatever happened to the OmegaMan? Could
CONvergence have been called MacroCon? Come and learn what CONvergence
could have looked like in an alternate universe!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Windy Bowlsby, Christopher Jones, Perrin Klumpp, Jeremy Stomberg, Video Team, Pat Wick, Tim Wick, Ishmael Williams</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>If you walk through the cave entrance, turn to page 27.</strong><br/>The
late 70's and early 80's saw a huge surge in popular solo role-playing
novels like Choose Your Own Adventure, Which Way, and many based on
table-top RPG's. Learn about new CYOA books and interactive DVDs being
published and share your favorites from the past.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rachel Kronick, Matt Savelkoul, Emily Stewart</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Copyright: Ethics in Action?</strong><br/>Copyright
affects us all, especially internet users. What's fair-game versus
out-and-out breaking of the law? Has Congress extended copyright too
many times? Shouldn't Mickey Mouse and Superman be in the public domain
by now?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Stephen J. Miller, Lars Pearson, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Land of 10,000 Filmmakers</strong><br/>The
local filmmaking scene has exploded in recent years. Hear from people
who have gone before you and learn how can you join in and make your
own production on a shoestring budget.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Tony Bruno, Jose' Figueroa, Troy LaFaye, Gordon Smuder, Rob Withoff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>3:10 to Serenity Valley</strong><br/>From
"Wagon Train to the Stars" to Firefly, Bravestarr, and Cowboy Bebop, a
number of series mix Western and SF genres, some more successfully than
others. Why does this unlikely combination manage to succeed?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Todd C. Hansen, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Michael Scott Shappe</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Open Discussion 1</strong><br/>Open Discussion - come and join the geek chat!<br/><font size="-1"><em></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Animation All-Stars</strong><br/>Explore
animation trends over time and learn what awaits us in the future of 2D
and 3D animation. How has creation and production changed?<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Video Team, Matt Waterhouse, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing Robert &amp; Daren</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Matrix Tag Special Event</strong><br/>Join
the Revolution&#8230;or fight it. Do you have what it takes to help Neo win
the war for Zion ? Or will you support Agent Smith in his quest to
subjugate the humans? In Matrix Tag, two teams vie for power over the
fate of the human race. Players choose the roles of Agent Smith, Neo,
Morpheus, Trinity, Agent and Zionist. Any number of people can play,
joining in and leaving at any time. Players are free to attend other
programming during the Convention, as they seek out Agents and Zionists
and gain strength for their team.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Etiquette at the Gaming Table</strong><br/>What are some basic do's and don'ts that everyone (including socially challenged geeks) should know?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Paula Fleming, Heather Johnson, Don Kaiser, Rachel Kronick, Stephen J. Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>How Comics Get Made</strong><br/>What
does it take to get a comic published? From a kernel of an concept to
the finished product on your local comic store shelf, here's an insight
into the comic publication industry.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Terry Beatty, Christopher Jones, Lars Pearson, Damian Sheridan, Gordon Smuder</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>CONvergence 201:  One of Us!  One of Us!</strong><br/>So
you've passed CONvergence 101. Or you are ready to take the plunge and
get involved with CONvergence... find out how you can volunteer, become
a part of our convention committee, and learn about the
behind-the-scenes machinations of the Connie Assembly Factory!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Windy Bowlsby, Jay Curry, Michael Lee</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Shadow Out of Lovecraft</strong><br/>HP Lovecraft was the greatest horror writer of the 20th century. What  
does that mean for us in the 21st?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dana M. Baird, Roy C. Booth, Pat Harrigan, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Melissa Kaercher, Tim Uren</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Gadget Gossip!</strong><br/>Looking
for that perfect cell phone? Wanting to go high-def? Share your
opinions and recommendations in this "Consumer Reports" style panel.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Hank Lederer</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>How To Be a Geek in the Workplace</strong><br/>What's
appropriate and not appropriate in a corporate setting? How can you
display your geek pride while keeping other nerdy habits in-check? Is
there a glass ceiling for geeks?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Mark Goldberg, Marie Hulslander, Jen Manna, Chris Pasquarette, Tracie Peters</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Globalization of Hollywood</strong><br/>Films
don&#8217;t have to be made in Hollywood anymore. In addition to filming in
different locations across the country and world, pre and post
production can happen anywhere. Come learn about this new phenomenon
and what goes on in home-studios.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Crist Ballas, Tony Bruno, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, Jose' Figueroa, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong>, Rob Withoff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Anime Essentials 101 aka "The First Hit Is Free!"</strong><br/>Thinking
about dipping your toes into the worlds of anime fandom? Wondering what
'all the kids are going on about?' Have you been trying to get your
friends into this fandom? Join us as we take the first steps into an
all-consuming addiction.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Alexandra Howes, Teresa Kramer, Rebecca Marjesdatter, Jo Thomsen, Aaron Vander Giessen, Matt Weinberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Open Discussion 2</strong><br/>Open Discussion - come and join the geek chat!<br/><font size="-1"><em></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Gosh, Golly, Gee Whiz: Days of Rocket Summer</strong><br/>Move
over Veronica Mars and remember back to a simpler time with thrilling
detective noir stories aimed at boys (and girls) of the 1940's - 60's
like Nancy Drew, Brains Benton, The Three Investigators, and The Mad
Scientists' Club. Join us for a nostalgic discussion of this genre or
discover it for the first time. We promise not to chloroform anyone at
the door!<br/><font size="-1"><em>G. David Nordley, Jason Tucker</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Superheroes Do Not Obey the Laws of Physics...</strong><br/>(but
they do remember anniversaries!)...Join Doctor Jim for his famous panel
discussing the physics of Superheroes using some specially tailored
examples made specifically for our convention.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing Mercedes &amp; Larry</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Paper Airplanes</strong><br/>Come
and learn to make a variety of paper airplanes. Which ones fly the
furthest? Let's test our creations out in the Garden Court!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Angie Anderson, Rachael Salisbury</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Whither OGL?</strong><br/>How
successful are open gaming licenses? How do companies like Atlas and
Fantasy Flight make use of OGL's and is there a case against using them?<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Stephen J. Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Gargoyles: The Continuing Saga</strong><br/>Join
guest of honor Greg Weisman as he discusses his popular creation and
shares how the story continues thanks to comic books and DVD releases.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Video Team, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Time Management 101: When Did Relaxing Become Stressful?</strong><br/>If
you're like the rest of us, you have a lot of unwatched DVDs sitting
around, stacks of comics in the "to read" pile, books overflowing, and
video games collecting dust. Let's come up with a strategy to make some
headway into our collections! By this time next year, let's get caught
up (or at least closer to where we want to be!)<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joel Arnold, Jay Curry, Taylor Kent, Marguerite Krause, Hilary Moon Murphy</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Long View: The Future of the High Fantasy Epic</strong><br/>How
do you sustain a story arc over multiple thick volumes? How do you
avoid repetition and keep everything coherent? What are some good and
bad examples of these epics?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eve Cain, David Margosian, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Where's My Flying Car?</strong><br/>A
"Roomba" hardly qualifies as a "Rosie the Robot" from the Jetsons.
Where's the shiny future we were promised back in the Tommorowland of
the 1950's?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Seth Chmelik, Hank Lederer, Jennifer Menken, G. David Nordley, Emily Stewart, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Art Show Primer</strong><br/>A
guided tour of the art show: where it is, what it is, how to get your
art in there, and how to get what you want out legally. Hosted by the
all star art show crew!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Charles Piehl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Which Non-Genre Films Should You See?</strong><br/>The
classic CONvergence panel returns... there is a world of film outside
typical sci-fi and fantasy fare. Come and get some suggestions to round
out your NetFlix queue!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Windy Bowlsby, Todd C. Hansen, Paul Harmeyer, Jason Tucker</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Lost</strong><br/>Are
you still watching Lost? Have you fallen out and want to get back in?
Are they off the island yet? Speculate as to what you think will happen
next and fill in people who've been away.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Alexandra Howes, Michael Lee, Derek Mahr, Erica Schaub</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Hulk Panel is Best One at Con!</strong><br/>Puny
humans think to harm Hulk. Even Banner betray Hulk. But Hulk will
smash! The madder Hulk is, the stronger Hulk gets. Hulk is the
strongest one there is!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman, Jonathan Palmer</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Dana M. Baird Reading</strong><br/>Join Dana M. Baird for a reading from one of her works.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dana M. Baird</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Theremin Through the Future!.</strong><br/>Is
the Theremin the last great futuristic instrument? What are some
examples of other ground-breaking musical instruments and technological
innovations in the last century?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Holly Day, Scott Keever, Caly McMorrow</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/Trace</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Make Your Own Voodoo Doll</strong><br/>You know you want to...muah ha ha!  We provide most of the material, you provide the nemesis.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Angie Anderson, Charlotte Nickerson</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Webkinz World</strong><br/>Webkinz
are stuffed animals that come with an 8-character code which allow you
to "adopt" your pet into the virtual Webkinz World. Come and learn
about this MMORPG for children and adults alike that features an
interactive safe environment with its own economy. Share any concerns
you have about this phenomenon sweeping elementary schools across the
nation. Parents welcome.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jan Dickinson, Hilary Moon Murphy</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Costuming 101: Masquerades and Hall Costumes</strong><br/>So you want to start showcasing, costuming, or cos-playing?  Where do you start and when do you kick it up a notch to compete?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Patrick Fisher, Mariah Fryer, Deborah Jones, Rhiannon Jones, Amada Marquez</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Reptiles</strong><br/>Come and look at reptiles up-close and learn about the animals.  Sponsored by MISFITS.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Clay Lamkin, Erin Lorenz, Sarah Richard</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Writing Folklore and Myth From Different Cultures</strong><br/>Asian,
Native American, Eastern European, and other non-Western European
cultures are often portrayed negatively or inaccurately in speculative
fiction. What are the dangers of cultural ignorance in world-building?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Roy C. Booth, Philip Kaveny, Chris Pasquarette, Damian Sheridan, Adam Stemple, Chuck Waibel</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Care and Feeding of Your Home Library</strong><br/>What
are your collecting habits when it comes to books? Do you buy a lot of
books or borrow them from the library? What makes you decide to
purchase a book? How do you store or display your collection?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Paula Fleming, Jenni Klumpp, Kelly McCullough, Juanita Nesbitt, Lynne Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Star Wars Prequels: Ten Years On</strong><br/>Where's
the love? Have you come over to the Dark Side and embraced the power of
the prequels? How have these films aged and do they stand the test of
time?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong>, Greg Prickman, Video Team, Aaron Vander Giessen, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>MST3K: The Local Legacy</strong><br/>Join
first-time CONvergence Guest of Honor Trace Beaulieu as he discusses
the local origins of MST3K and his involvement as the diabolical Dr.
Forrester and original voice of Crow T. Robot, as well as his work
behind the scenes on the show.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Odyssey: Sir Arthur C. Clarke, 1917-2008</strong><br/>Let's
memorialize the life and work of the author of Childhood's End,
Profiles of the Future, 2001: A Space Odyssey, Rendezvous with Rama,
and The Fountains of Paradise.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman, Paul F. Richards</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Afternoon Reading with David</strong><br/>Join David Weber for an intimate reading in the Dorian Gray Memorial Literary Lounge.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>David Weber</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Vidders' Delight</strong><br/>From
its analog start in the mid 1970's to its widespread digital enjoyment
today, fans have been 'vidding' for years. Come and learn about the
history of fan music video tributes and see some fine examples.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Lori Fischer, Jo Thomsen</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Mark &amp; Bernie</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Steam Century Mystery LARP</strong><br/>The
Steam Century Mystery LARP is a multifaceted game that combines
elements of live action roleplaying and crime dramas. Players follow a
trail of clues by investigating rooms, speaking to costumed characters
and playing games of skill. Players sign up at game registration and
attend a 30 minute orientation which explains the world of Steam
Century and how to interact with props and characters.
Game play takes place over a set period of time, but is designed to be
played intermittently. Players are encouraged to take part in other con
activities during the game. Characters and clues can be found
throughout the con. Runs Friday 5 PM - Midnight.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Indie Games</strong><br/>Come and share your finds from independent homebrew and smaller publishers that you've discovered.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Rachel Kronick, Stephen J. Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doll Making and Doll Collecting</strong><br/>From porcelain to Asian ball joint dolls, discuss doll building, doll dressing, and doll collecting.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Lori Fischer, Mara Kapp, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Imperfect Heroes</strong><br/>Series
like Dexter, House M.D., The Shield, and Monk feature abrasive lead
characters. We see this in comics, films, videogames, and novels too.
Do we love these characters all the more because of their flaws and
imperfections? Can a character become too "out there" to like? When do
they become anti-heroes?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Beitscher, Erika Kinsman, Marguerite Krause, G. David Nordley, Chris Pasquarette, Bob Wagner</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Writing Contest Recpeption</strong><br/>Come
and meet some of the winners of the MISFITS Annual Writing Contest and
learn about how you or your children can participate in the annual
contest.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joel Arnold, Jodie Gustafson, Charlotte Nickerson, Jody Wurl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>How Do You Say That in Klingon?</strong><br/>A panel about translating and an easy introduction to the Warrior's tongue.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Bill Hedrick, Christopher Kidder, Laura Thurston</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Prop Building</strong><br/>Prop-builder
and physical effects artist Christian Colquhoun's projects have
included Galaxy Quest, Van Helsing, and Firefly. Come and learn about
the art of prop design and construction.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>July '07 - July '08 Films:  Annual Review</strong><br/>The
good, the bad, and the ugly are up for discussion in our annual review
of science-fiction, fantasy, and horror films from the past 365 days.
What worked? What didn't?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Melissa Kaercher, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, Jeremy Stomberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doctor Who by Decade: The Seventies</strong><br/>Covering
the 1970's era Dr. Who, this is the second in a series of four panels
exploring the rich and varied history of the classic British
science-fiction series, focusing on the Pertwee and T. Baker eras.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Ellis, Brian Jonas, Michael Lee, Emily Stewart, Michael Zecca</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Twin Cities Speculative Fiction Writers Network Meeting</strong><br/>Come learn about this resource for local aspiring science fiction and fantasy writers.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Merriam</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Art of Soundtracks</strong><br/>What
are some of your favorite soundtracks and composers? How does the art
of music enhance the movie-going, video game-playing, or TV-watching
experience? Which soundtracks detract and distract you from the source
material?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Holly Day, Cabell Gathman, Scott Keever, David Margosian, Juanita Nesbitt, Stephan Stomberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Wally &amp; Greg</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Game Design</strong><br/>Learn about the process of designing games.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, <strong>John Kovalic</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Give those Nymphs Some Hooters: Anniversary Edition</strong><br/>Join
us for our annual discussion of the feminine image in sci-fi and
fantasy (including the huge breasts in comics, anime, and manga).<br/><font size="-1"><em>Mariah Fryer, Melissa Gregory, Alexandra Howes, Jen Manna, Amada Marquez</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Cell vs. Chip</strong><br/>Hand-drawn
cell animation vs. computer animation - do you have a preference? Do
you care, as long as the final product is done well?<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Margosian, Jennifer Menken, Matt Waterhouse, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Getting Published 101</strong><br/>Looking
to get famous and make lots of money writing? How about a more
realistic view of the writing and publishing process? We'll cover
prepping a work for submission (including cover letters and business
writing) to coping with rejection.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jerrod Balzer, Cynthia Booth, Roy C. Booth, Garnet Gyre, Philip Kaveny, Michael Merriam</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Digital Distribution Debate</strong><br/>Some
say the Blu-Ray era will be very short-lived as everyone moves to
digital downloads. Is this true? iTunes and physical CDs have
co-existed nicely over the past six years - will that model hold true
for video media? Do we currently have the telecommunication and storage
infrastructure to support 50 GB downloads?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Aaron Vander Giessen</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Where to Shop?</strong><br/>What
type of bookstore do you support and why? Do you go with the local
indie store, a chain like B&amp;N, or do you find yourself shopping on
Abe Books or Amazon?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Miranda Cole, Taylor Kent, Greg Ketter, Ann Laabs, Laine Worth</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Film Remakes: Exhuming the Past?</strong><br/>Everything
old is new again. Why can't Hollywood come up with a new idea? Do new
interpretations of classic movies have their own merit?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Beitscher, Todd C. Hansen, S.D. Hintz, Stephan Stomberg, Jason D. Wittman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doctor Who: Series Four</strong><br/>This
panel discusses Donna Noble's year aboard the TARDIS and will contain
spoilers and speculation around Series Four of Doctor Who and beyond.
Also, what can we look forward to during the "gap year?"<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Lee, Steven Manfred, Kelly McCullough, Lynne Thomas, Michael Zecca</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Joel Arnold Reading</strong><br/>Join Joel Arnold for a reading from one of his works.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joel Arnold</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Digital Video Production</strong><br/>Learn about the science and computer programs behind a successful production shot on digital video.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Tony Bruno, Scott Keever, Troy LaFaye, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, Rob Withoff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 6:30pm - 7:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/Mark &amp; Marv</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>I Can Has Fluidic Beverage?</strong><br/>The
history of drinking games, with props. Featuring bar tricks, and rules
to some of the geekiest drinking games around. Hotel room not included.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Emily Stewart, Laura Thurston</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>GLBT Comic Characters</strong><br/>Northstar
is no longer the only gay in the village. We've got Hulkling, Wiccan,
Batwoman, and many others. Discuss your faves and speculate which other
characters still need to come out?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jonathan Palmer, Jason Tucker, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Beyond "Weekend Update"</strong><br/>There
was a time when SNL's "Weekend Update" was our only source for
sarcastic takes on news events. Now, we've got fake news in multiple
media, including newspaper, blogs - The Onion, Jon Stewart, Steven
Colbert, and others. What are your favorites and what makes this
sub-genre so appealing to SF&amp;F fans?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Ellis, Terry Faust, Paula Fleming, David E. Romm</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Philip Pullman - The Anti-Narnia</strong><br/>Discuss
the "His Dark Materials" trilogy and Lyra's Oxford novella. What are
Pullman's plans for "The Book of Dust" and other entries in this
universe?<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Emerson, Alexandra Howes, Philip Kaveny, Amada Marquez, Heidi Waterhouse</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Martial Arts Demonstration</strong><br/>Not
all the stunts you see in a martial arts movie are done using computer
graphics, blue screen, and
wires. Most of the stunts are based on real martial arts applications
that require of years of practice to perfect. Come see a martial arts
demonstration with Jose Figueroa, owner of Dark Raven Studios<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jose' Figueroa</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Trek on Film</strong><br/>From
Robert Wise to J.J. Abrams and Roddenberry to Berman - let's discuss
the past and future of the Star Trek cinematic experience.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, <strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, Rob Johnson, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, Michael Scott Shappe, Joan Marie Verba</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Heroes: Volume Two</strong><br/>The
truncated second season of Heroes divided many fans. What worked and
what could have been improved during Heroes' sophomoric effort? What's
in store for season three and what have the web-comics added? The
Company requests you check your mind control abilities at the door
please.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Christa Dickson, Steve Erickson, Erica Schaub</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 2:00am</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Tales of the Unanticipated Not-a-Publication Party</strong><br/>Hang
out with the staff of and contributors to this 22-year-old fiction
antholo-zine, the 29th issue of which will premiere at Diversicon in
August. See lots of cool back issues! Party goes until 1 AM.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 8:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Local Filmmaker Film Clips</strong><br/>Join us in the A/V room for a taste of local productions shot in and around the Twin Cities area.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Britt Aamodt, Tony Bruno, Troy LaFaye, Michael Malver, Rob Withoff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 2:00am</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Late Night Accoustic Music (Friday)</strong><br/>Space reserved for late night accoustic music collaboration.  Noise restrictions until midnight because of other panels.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Becca Leathers</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Web Comics</strong><br/>What
are some of your favorite web-comics? How long have you been reading
them? Share your favorites and discover some new ones.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Lori Fischer, Sarah Hertz, Jen Manna, Boris Smelov</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Geek Speed Dating</strong><br/>Join in as we put an unique spin on this modern phenomenon.  How many three minute dates can you fit into an hour?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Melissa Gregory</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Managing the Mega-Series</strong><br/>Sometimes
other authors work in the sandbox you've created, like David Weber's
Honor-verse. How do you oversee and manage such an endeavor?<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>David Weber</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Dangerous Days: Dystopias</strong><br/>The
end is near friends - or at least that's what Hollywood wants you to
think. What would you do if you were a character in a film like 28 Days
Later or I Am Legend to live long enough to make it to the end credits?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Patrick Allen, Cabell Gathman, Tangee Harrison, Taylor Kent, Jennifer Menken, Matt Merfeld</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Torchwood</strong><br/>Beyond
the government, yada yada yada. Basically, this is an hour long
opportunity to squee over Ianto, Captain Jack, and Captain John. Oh and
talk about how much an improvement the second series was over the first
as well.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Christa Dickson, James Gottfried, Mara Kapp, Charlie Paulsen, Lynne Thomas, Dayna Jean Wolter</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Star Trek Remastered</strong><br/>The
original Star Trek series is airing across the country in
high-definition with enhanced special effects. Learn about the genesis
of this project and what could have been...<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Sophisticated Sewing</strong><br/>Sewing and tailoring tips from experienced costumers. How to get the effects you want, and make your costumes really stand out.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Bill Hedrick, Deborah Jones, Rhiannon Jones, Gwen Kachelmyer, Rae Lundquist</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Pun-El</strong><br/>We're baaack!  Our yearly painful Punnel voyage returns.  Be afraid.  Be very afraid.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ed Eastman, Boris Smelov</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Guilty Pleasures</strong><br/>The long requested return of a CONvergence favorite.  Come clean and share your literary guilty pleasures with everyone!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Nessa Fedde, Doug Texter, Heidi Waterhouse, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>How to Take Over the World!</strong><br/>Join
some super-villain panelists and learn the proper way to take over the
world. We'll explain our plan in detail to you and entertain
suggestions (but not if you're a tied-up superhero - we're smarter than
that!)<br/><font size="-1"><em>Cynthia Booth, Roy C. Booth, Eve Cain, Amada Marquez, Chris Pasquarette</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Sci-fi Saturdays</strong><br/>Believe
it or not, made-for-TV movies like Mansquito are some of the highest
rated fare on the network and sell reasonably well on DVD as well.
Who&#8217;s watching these movies and why? Does it go beyond typical MST3K
train-wreck fascination? What are some of your favorite classic
B-Movies?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Beitscher, Paul Harmeyer, Alexandra Howes, Taylor Kent, Karen Joan Kohoutek, George Richard</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Rebirth of the Heroine</strong><br/>While
not quite up to the Xena glory days of the late 1990's - has there
finally been a feminist resurgence of television heroines as of late
with Sarah Connor, the Bionic Woman, and others? Or are we seeing
watered-down Ghost Whisperers?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jen Manna, Charlotte Nickerson, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Friday Night Bedtime Stories with the 'Pods</strong><br/>Escape
Pod, Pseudo Pod, and Pod Castle ... three weekly audio casts from the
Escape Artists! Come and listen to a bed-time story with some of the
latest and greatest of these audio giants of Science Fiction, Horror,
and Fantasy! Join us on the 22nd floor in 2201 for back-to-back stories
of speculation, fantasy, and fun. Wear your fluffy bunny slippers and
bathrobe, if you like ... just come prepared to listen to some really
great tales of modern SF!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Rust</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Fri 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Soylent Blue</strong><br/>Soylent Blue returns!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Kelvin Hatle, ASL Interpreter, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Drawing with Christopher Jones</strong><br/>Adults and kids alike are welcome to spend an hour with Christopher  
Jones, either drawing or listening to Chris' stories about his work  
in comics or creating artwork for CONvergence.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Christopher Jones</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Aerobics with Cleo</strong><br/>Join
Cleo on Saturday morning for our annual aerobics fitness panel. Bring
your workout shoes and dress comfortably. Fun music and a supportive
atmosphere supplied, you bring the rest!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Amada Marquez</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Young Adult Literature</strong><br/>Our
popular Saturday Morning panel is back. Share your favorite young adult
fantasy series of yesteryear and discuss what's new in Children's Lit
in the past year.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Heidi Johnson, Jen Manna, Joan Marquez, Amanda Newman, Catherine Schaff-Stump, Beth Scudder, Electra Vincent</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Saturday Morning Cartoons Made Me Gay!</strong><br/>Looking
back at popular performers from our childhood who were gay (Paul Lynde,
Charles Nelson Reilly, Dick Sargent) or who had gay sensibilities
(Jonathan Harris, John Ritter) as well as cartoon characters from the
era (He-Man, Superfriends, Lidsville, etc) it's clear to see the gay
subtext or sensibility. What effect did these characters and icons have
on us? Did they help us become who we are?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joe Agee, Andrew Berthke, Paul Harmeyer, Don Kaiser, Claudia Slovacek, Jason Tucker</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Art of Movie Posters</strong><br/>Movie
posters are just as collectible as old film reels (sometimes more so).
What are your favorite movie posters and what rarities are you still
seeking? Do the movie posters today live up to the golden age of
yesteryear?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Science!</strong><br/>Join
our science guests of honor as they demonstrate some simple and basic
science experiments (like a wave machine and miniature volcano) using
easy to find household items.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Wii: The Changing Face of Gaming</strong><br/>How
has the Wii changed the face of gaming? Has it brought back people
who've been away from the home console scene? Is there more to the Wii
than news stories about its use in retirement homes?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Andrew Davies, Matt Everhart, Shannon Grady, Tim Wick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Working in Comics</strong><br/>What is it like working in the comic industry as a livelihood?  What's the day to day working grind like?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Terry Beatty, Christopher Jones, Melissa Kaercher</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Return of the Clubs!</strong><br/>A
long-standing convention tradition, the club fan-faire has returned in
a new format. Come and learn about local fan clubs specializing in a
variety of genres and public service. There's a club out there for
everyone! Come and promote your local fan organization.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Seth Chmelik, Ed Cook, Jodie Gustafson, Gwen Kachelmyer, Neil Monson, John Neitz</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Living with a Writer</strong><br/>Significant others of writers and artist trade stories and tips about the joys and challenges of living with a creative person.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Cynthia Booth, Jennifer Lynch, Sherry Merriam</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Parrots as Companions</strong><br/>The
Parrot Adoption Education Program invites you to see companion birds up
close, learn about the animals, and the non-profit organization that is
involved in the rehabilitation and fostering of companion parrots.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Gail Hildebrand, Jeff Hildebrand, Renee Quimby</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>High Level Creativity</strong><br/>Fandom
tends to attract those with imaginations. A high level of creativity is
prevalent in everything from writing, art and costuming, to designing
game campaigns for your friends. Come and discuss these unique traits
for both individuals and as a community in general.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Holly Day, Paula Fleming, Laramie Sasseville, Gordon Smuder, Dave Walbridge, Anna Waltz</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Blurring of the Lines</strong><br/>Movies
like Sin City, Sky Captain, The Spirit, and Beowulf have blurred the
lines between live action and computer-generated animation. What films
have benefited from this merging of technology and which stories are
ideal for this approach in the future?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Jeremy Stomberg, Matt Waterhouse</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Renaissance of Buffy &amp; Angel</strong><br/>It's
time to revisit the epic saga of Buffy and Angel. All 254 episodes of
it and how it's continuing thanks to comic books and novels.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jerrod Balzer, Christa Dickson, Philip Kaveny, Lars Pearson, Michael D. Thomas, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Open Discussion 3</strong><br/>Open Discussion - come and join the geek chat!<br/><font size="-1"><em></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Michael Merriam Reading</strong><br/>Join Michael Merriam for a reading from one of his works.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Merriam</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Shiny New Anime</strong><br/>A
guide to the latest and greatest animated efforts hailing from Japan.
Come and see what you can look forward to in future releases, get some
recommendations, and review what's been released in the past 365 days.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jessi Silver, Boris Smelov, Jo Thomsen</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Len &amp; Bernie</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Origami</strong><br/>Learn the basics of this beautiful and ancient Japanese art of paper folding.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Angie Anderson</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Women and Gaming</strong><br/>Yes
we play them! Why don't the game companies realize that they write for
an audience that includes women? There's more out there than Cooking
Mama and the Imagine series, after all...<br/><font size="-1"><em>Nessa Fedde, Mariah Fryer, Beth Kinderman, Rachel Kronick, Jen Manna, Laine Worth</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Secret Origins of Swamp Thing</strong><br/>Join
the co-creators of Swamp Thing and learn about how the character came
about and which direction Len and Bernie would like to see their
creation progress.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Morris Dance Workshop</strong><br/>Learn
about this form of English folk dance accompanied by music. It is based
on rhythmic stepping and the execution of choreographed figures by a
group of dancers.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Don Kaiser</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Works of Mercedes Lackey</strong><br/>Join
Mercedes Lackey for an hour-long discussion of her body of work to date
and her plans for future novels, moderated by David Lenander, a member
of The Rivendell Group, a fantasy book discussion group that has met
regularly since 1973.<br/><font size="-1"><em>ASL Interpreter, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, David Lenander, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Not All FTL Drives Are Made the Same</strong><br/>Debate the advantages and disadvantages of various theoretical  faster-than-light spaceship drives.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Seth Chmelik, Craig Finseth, G. David Nordley, Pat Sullivan</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Evolution of Social Networking</strong><br/>From
local bulletin board forums, newsgroups, and IRC to the modern
labyrinth of FaceBook and MySpace, how have message boards changed over
time? You may be surprised that some of your old haunts aren't as
abandoned as you think!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Lee, Greg Prickman, Michael Scott Shappe, Aaron Vander Giessen</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Pixar Panel</strong><br/>Talkies?
Is the fad over? How brilliant is Pixar's Wall-E? Is dialogue
overrated? Discuss the recent film and how it holds up to Pixar's other
releases.<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Margosian, Jennifer Menken, Matt Waterhouse</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>To Boldly Go: The History and Future of Star Trek</strong><br/>Celebrate
the rich history of Star Trek as we review what has come before. If
you've fallen out of Trek in the last few years, come back and
rediscover what you loved about it in the first place.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, <strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Writing Business: Cover letters, manuscripts, and rejections</strong><br/>Back
to basics. There are books that handle this topic fairly well, but
nothing substitutes for experience. Active pros and semi-pros in
writing, editing and publishing talk about the dos and don'ts.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Roy C. Booth, Holly Day, Kelly McCullough, Michael Merriam, Adam Stemple, Anna Waltz</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Podcasting</strong><br/>Do
you want to learn how to start your own podcast? What are some of the
best podcasts out there to learn from? What software and equipment do
you need to get started?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Shannon Grady, Taylor Kent, Troy LaFaye, Tim Wilsie</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Trace B.</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Reaper Miniature Demonstration</strong><br/>Join
one of Reaper's Black Lightning representatives for a "paint and take"
party. All paints, brushes, and miniatures will be provided.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Erin Warfield</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Corset-making</strong><br/>Share your successes in corset design and building.  What are some pitfalls to avoid?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dana M. Baird, Eve Cain, Mariah Fryer, Amada Marquez</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Puppetry!</strong><br/>From
MST3K to the Muppet Show, Farscape to Captain Scarlet, The Dark Crystal
to Yoda, there have been a number of series and movies that used
puppets as characters. Discuss your favorites and learn about current
puppet-related shows.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong>, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, David Margosian, Gordon Smuder</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Legion of the All-Stars</strong><br/>Join
many of our comic book guests of honor in a wide-ranging roundtable
discussion of a 'state of the union' of the comics industry.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Christopher Jones, Video Team, Dan Wallace, <strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Green Panel</strong><br/>Many
scientists agree that Global Warming is a real threat to the future of
Mankind. Some disagree. What do you think? What about alternatives to
oil and other power sources? Where's our personal fusion reactors?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matthew Lee Davis, Ken Konkol, G. David Nordley, Emily Stewart, Chuck Waibel</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Caring For Your Collection</strong><br/>What's
the best way to store and display your geek collection? Share ideas,
best practices, and things to avoid when it comes to home and apartment
display of DVDs, games, comics, artwork, etc.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Melissa Kaercher, Jenni Klumpp, Tim Wick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Trilogy Limitations: What happened to the franchise?</strong><br/>Shrek
the Third, Pirates 3, Spider-Man 3 - what happened to these movie
franchises? Why stop at three films? Should they have stopped at one?
Are we suffering from "Franchise Fatigue?"<br/><font size="-1"><em>Garnet Gyre, Derek Mahr</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Battlestar Galactica: Legacy</strong><br/>The
final season of Battlestar Galactica is upon us. Will the Colonial
Fleet find Earth? Who is the final Cylon? Will the Caprica prequel be
any good? Whatever the answers, the reimangined BSG series has set the
bar so high in terms of acting, story, and effects, that any genre show
coming in its footsteps will have awfully big shoes to fill.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Julie Graves, Philip Kaveny, Michael Scott Shappe, Scott Smith, Jason D. Wittman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Works of David Weber</strong><br/>Com
and hear David Weber talk about his work. Discussion sponsored by
Second Foundation, a speculative fiction book discussion group that has
met regularly since 1983.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman, ASL Interpreter, Polly Jo Peterson, Video Team, <strong>David Weber</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Wonder Twin Science Powers Activate!</strong><br/>Dr. Jim and Bridget Landry sharing the stage at last, by popular demand!  Learn about their ongoing projects and research!<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Scrapbooking</strong><br/>Share
scrapbooking techniques and learn the in's and out's of one of the
fastest growing hobbies in the United States. There are many creative
ways to display your CONvergence photo memories.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Teri Blauer, Geoff Williams</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Console Wars II: The Sequel</strong><br/>We're
another year into the life-cycles of the X-Box 360, Nintendo Wii, and
Playstation 3. Have there been any big surprises over the past year?
How will Blu-Ray victory, the Red Ring of Death, direct downloads, and
the casual gaming market influence console choice? Is it high-time
everyone just goes multi-console and buys all three?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matt Everhart, Scott Smith</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Non-Superhero Comic Books</strong><br/>Share
some of your favorite comic books that don't involve super heroes or
super-powered characters like "Y: The Last Man" and others.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Terry Beatty, David Emerson, Patrick Fisher, Jonathan Palmer, Lars Pearson, Damian Sheridan</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>What Does Franchise Continuity Mean to You?</strong><br/>Continuity,
or what is canon, is a very personal thing.<br/> Which Buffy Season 8
do you count - the comic version, the novels, or both?<br/> Do you
consider animated Trek the last two years of the 5-year mission?<br/>
Where do Doctor Who audios fit in?<br/> What about the Babylon 5 comic
books or Star Wars video games? Or does it even matter at all?<br/>
Remember - no one is "right" or "wrong" - come and share some of your
more inventive and interesting canon theories in this respectful
round-table discussion.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Paul Harmeyer, Christopher Jones, Michael Lee, Video Team, Michael D. Thomas, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Influence of Classic Lit</strong><br/>How does classic literature tie into and influence speculative fiction?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matthew Lee Davis, Ann Laabs, Doug Texter, Heidi Waterhouse, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Engineering Hollywood Robots</strong><br/>When trying to build a famous robot like Robbie, what can actually be
achieved, what's infeasable, and what can be improved upon?  Sponsored by the Twin Cities Robotics Club.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Richard Caylor, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, William Crolley, Terry Faust, Bill McTeer, Bob Odegard, Michael Walsh</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Fun Tai Chi Games for All Ages</strong><br/>This
workshop teaches the basics of tai chi through a series of simple
games. Each of these games are
cooperative in nature, and leads to the true essence of taiji which is
to become one with your partner.
This workshop also demonstrates how to adapt each game to everyone's
ability. Bring your sense of humor and be be prepared to have a blast!!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jose' Figueroa</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Kingdom of the Crystal Skull</strong><br/>The
man in the hat is back. Was the latest Indiana Jones Adventure
everything we were hoping or did Spielberg pull a Lucas on us? Dust off
your bullwhip and discuss any Indy topics that strike your fancy!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Mike Helde, Troy LaFaye, Dan Wallace, Tim Wick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Reimagining of TV Shows</strong><br/>It
seems like the movie-remake craze of the past several years has
filtered down to our television sets. What makes a remake successful?
When should a show be rebooted (BSG) vs. making it a continuation
(Trek: Next Gen, Doctor Who)?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Derek Mahr, Joan Marie Verba</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Where Should We Go in Space?</strong><br/>Should
we emphasize human or robotic expeditions? How should we replace the
shuttle? Should we expand on the space station? Should we go back to
the Moon and build a permanent outpost? Should we make a human
expedition to Mars? Should we search Europa's ocean for life? And? Or?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Paul F. Richards</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Broad Universe Rapidfire Reading</strong><br/>This is a fiction reading by members of Broad Universe, an organization which promotes the work of women SF&amp;F writers.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Catherine Lundoff, Sharon K. Richards, Ruth Souther, Kathryn Sullivan</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Science of Effects</strong><br/>Just
how much does science factor into set and effects designs? Is there a
point where science is thrown out to achieve the 'cool' factor?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Crist Ballas, <strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/Peter &amp; John</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>John Kovalic</strong>, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Caped Wonder!</strong><br/>Create
your own superhero! First, think of what your superhero's powers and
training are. Then create a name for your character. Finally, design a
symbol, make a cape, and even a mask.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rachael Salisbury</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Kovalic!</strong><br/>Spend
an hour with John Kovalic, a game designer and illustrator. Maybe
you'll even learn the secret history of Apples to Apples.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>John Kovalic</strong>, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>CLAMP</strong><br/>A discussion of the works of Japan's premiere women's comic book/manga collective.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Melissa Gregory, Catherine Lundoff, Rebecca Marjesdatter</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Raptor Center</strong><br/>Come and look at birds of prey up-close and learn about the animals.  Sponsored by MISFITS.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Amber Burnett, <strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, Erin Lorenz, Sharon Steitler</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Good, the Bad, and the *SHUSH*!</strong><br/>How
accurately have librarians been portrayed in books, comics, television,
and movies? Meet some real-life librarians and get their take on
popular culture's interpretation of their livelihood.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jenni Klumpp, Kevin McIntyre, Greg Prickman, Lynne Thomas, Jody Wurl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Moonshot in '69: Wha' Happened?</strong><br/>Feel
like interest in manned space exploration has taken one giant leap
backwards since the 1960's? What can be done to get the public excited
for space exploration? Do we need an imminent natural disaster calling
for planetary evacuation to get butts moving? Or just another Cold War?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Huset, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong>, G. David Nordley, Chuck Waibel</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Here Be Dragons...</strong><br/>Dragons
exist in many mythologies and cultures the world over. Come and learn
about the different myths and legends surrounding these creatures.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Philip Kaveny, Jason D. Wittman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Spoiler Alert: The Rumor Mill</strong><br/>Let's
roll up the sleeves, get our hands dirty, and dish the dirt on upcoming
features. If you don't like spoilers and speculation then now would be
a good time to head to the project room.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Derek Mahr</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doctor Who by Decade: The Eighties</strong><br/>Covering
the 1980's era Dr. Who, this is the third in a series of four panels
exploring the rich and varied history of the classic British
science-fiction series, focusing on the Davison, C. Baker, and McCoy
eras. It probably would have been easier to say the JNT era, huh?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Lee, Charlie Paulsen, Lars Pearson, Michael Scott Shappe, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>SF Writing Groups: The 2008 Scene</strong><br/>This
annual gathering allows representatives of writing groups specializing
in science fiction and fantasy to report on how their groups function,
and gives groups that are looking for new members a chance to connect
with individuals who are interested in joining an SF writing group,
and/or gives individuals a chance to put their heads together and start
a new writing group. Sponsored at a local con since 1986 (formerly
Minicon, now CONvergence) by the Minnesota Imaginative Fiction Writers'
Alliance.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Ten Years with Connie: The Art of CONvergence</strong><br/>Connie creator Christopher Jones shares some highlights of 10 years  
of CONvergence artwork, and talks about the creation of Connie,  
Professor Maxwell Misfittle, and other CONvergence artwork and  
characters.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Christopher Jones</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/David</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>David Weber</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 6:30pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Sci-Fi Summit: The Mega-Panel</strong><br/>We've
got a panel so broad, so deep, and so miscellaneous in focus, we've had
to give it not one, but two time slots. Join us for an extended
mega-panel that covers sci-fi and fantasy trends in the past ten years
in books, movies, and television.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Christa Dickson, Ben Ellis, Lars Pearson, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 7:00pm - 9:00pm</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Masqurade</strong><br/>Our annual masqurade.<br/><font size="-1"><em></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 8:00pm - 2:00am</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>A Party for Readers and Viewers: The Silver Edition</strong><br/>Sponsored
by Second Foundation, a Twin Cities speculative fiction book-discussion
group - whose members are also film buffs - that has met regularly
since 1/29/1983. Goes from 8 PM until 2 AM.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:00pm - 11:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Art Auction</strong><br/>Our Annual Art Auction.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, Melissa Kaercher, Charles Piehl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Matrix Tag (14 and Up)</strong><br/>Join
the Revolution&#8230;or fight it. Do you have what it takes to help Neo win
the war for Zion ? Or will you support Agent Smith in his quest to
subjugate the humans? In Matrix Tag, two teams vie for power over the
fate of the human race. Players choose the roles of Agent Smith, Neo,
Morpheus, Trinity, Agent and Zionist. Any number of people can play,
joining in and leaving at any time. Players are free to attend other
programming during the Convention, as they seek out Agents and Zionists
and gain strength for their team.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jack Barker, Shannon Green, Rich Miller</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 2:00am</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Late Night Accoustic Music (Saturday)</strong><br/>Space reserved for late night accoustic music collaboration.  Noise restrictions until midnight because of other panels.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Becca Leathers</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Previously... in the Whedon-verse</strong><br/>Buffy,
Angel, and Firefly have gotten a new lease on life in a comic book
medium. Come and discuss the recent Firefly mini-series, Buffy Season
Eight, and Angel Season Six.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Mark Goldberg, Charlotte Nickerson</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Speculative Fiction and Sexuality</strong><br/>How
does Speculative Fiction approach sex and sexuality? Should there be
more examples of different kinds of sexuality identity and orientation
than what we're given in speculative literature? What are some good
examples of books that have done it right?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Bob Alberti, Eve Cain, Cabell Gathman, Hilary Moon Murphy, Damian Sheridan, Doug Texter, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Biology of Aliens</strong><br/>A
semi-serious take on the biology of aliens. How might they function?
What would their organs be like and would they be carbon-based life
forms?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Craig Finseth, Lori Fischer, Hank Lederer, G. David Nordley</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">A8<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Overuse of Iconic Sci-Fi and Fantasy Imagery?</strong><br/>Just
how many prints of unicorns, fairies, and dragons do we need? What are
some underused imagery you'd like to see drawings or paintings of
instead?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Chris Pasquarette, Laramie Sasseville</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Comics as Movies</strong><br/>Discuss
the recent slate of summer comic book movies including Iron Man,
Incredible Hulk, The Dark Knight, and others. How successful were they
(or do you think they will be) and what did they get right/wrong
compared to the source material? How will "The Marvel Masterpan" turn
out over the next few years?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Britt Aamodt, Terry Beatty, David Emerson, Taylor Kent, Jonathan Palmer, Dan Wallace, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 9:30pm - 10:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Pushing Daisies</strong><br/>Bring
a piece of pie and curl up on a chair as we discuss what is quite
possibly one of the most interesting new series of the past decade.
Just don't accidentally touch your neighbor!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dana M. Baird, Jenni Klumpp</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Comics for Mature Audiences</strong><br/>There
are numerous comics aimed at a more adult audience that deal with
mature themes of violence and sexuality. What are some of the best in
this genre? Which publishers have been neglecting their mature lines?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eve Cain, Hank Luttrell, Jennifer Menken, Damian Sheridan, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Urban Fantasy</strong><br/>The
borders of faerie have moved from pastoral England to modern cities.
What is the appeal of urban fantasy? Who writes the best stuff?<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Kelly McCullough, Michael Merriam, Juanita Nesbitt, Adam Stemple, Jody Wurl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Cool Britannia</strong><br/>Doctor
Who isn't the only British import worth checking out. There has been a
resurgence of sci-fi in the UK recently. Come learn about other series
worth your while, like Primeval, Life on Mars, Hyperdrive, Jekyll, and
many others.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ben Ellis, Brian Jonas, Michael Lee, Michael Zecca</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Saturday Night Bedtime Stories with the 'Pods</strong><br/>Escape
Pod, Pseudo Pod, and Pod Castle ... three weekly audio casts from the
Escape Artists! Come and listen to a bed-time story with some of the
latest and greatest of these audio giants of Science Fiction, Horror,
and Fantasy! Join us on the 22nd floor in 2201 for back-to-back stories
of speculation, fantasy, and fun. Wear your fluffy bunny slippers and
bathrobe, if you like ... just come prepared to listen to some really
great tales of modern SF!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Rust</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sat 11:00pm - 11:59pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>AV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Killer B's Improv Movie Show</strong><br/>Returning for its second year, the Killer B's Improv Movie Show will  
give new life to those crappy B-movies of yesteryear. In front of  
your eyes, our team of experts will create brand-new dialogue (and a  
whole new Theremin score!) for some of the worst film clips ever  
placed on celluloid.  The catch?  They've never seen the movies  
before!  It's a movie and live improv comedy at the same time.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jerry Belich, Kelvin Hatle, Melissa Kaercher, Scott Keever, Joe Scrimshaw, Tim Uren, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">101<br/>Proj</td><td valign="top"><strong>Storytime</strong><br/>Caryn's annual storytime featuring reading aloud, coloring books, and surprises!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Caryn Lengkeek</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Game Mastering</strong><br/>Being
a successful game or dungeon-master doesn't necessarily come easy. What
does it truly take to run a successful and memorable campaign? What
happens when you've thought of ten ways to solve a problem and your
players pick number eleven? How can you go about leaving your players
satisfied and wanting more?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Bob Alberti, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Rob Johnson, Rachel Kronick</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Crafty Geek Meet Up</strong><br/>Knit,
sew, scrapbook, bead, or just sit and chat about your favorite
projects. Learn a little about the local MISFITS crafty club while
you're at it!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Wendy Bock, Jodie Gustafson</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Kenpo Martial Arts</strong><br/>Join
us on Sunday morning for a fitness panel structured around Ed Parker's
Kenpo System (a martial arts discipline). Sweat a bit, learn a little
self-defense, and see some cool martial arts stuff inspired from movies.<br/><font size="-1"><em>John Shea</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Hogwarts Graduation!</strong><br/>The
seventh (and as of this writing) final novel in the Harry Potter saga
has been out for about a year, but there is still plenty to talk about!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Ryan Frank, Mara Kapp, Amanda Newman, Chris Stenzel, Geoff Williams, Gina Williams</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Yes Virginia, There Are Still Radio Hams!</strong><br/>Ham-radio
has been around for many years. Some might even call it a precursor to
the internet chat-room. What's the status of ham-radio in America and
if you are interested in pursuing this hobby, how do you get started?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jay Curry, Ed Eastman, Ben Huset</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>In Through the Out Door: A History of Special Effects</strong><br/>From
the beginnings in films like King Kong and Metropolis to modern-day
blockbusters, special effects have enhanced the movie-going experience.
Join us on this fantastical voyage.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Crist Ballas, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, Mark Goldberg, Gordon Smuder</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 9:30am - 10:30am</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Sarah Jane Adventures</strong><br/>It
may be the least talked about/acknowledged of the current run of Doctor
Who spin-offs, but it's definitely worth discussion. Is The Sarah Jane
Adventures far better than it has any right to be?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rob Callahan, Heidi Johnson, Steven Manfred, Lynne Thomas, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Local Gaming</strong><br/>How
does one go about finding a local group of geeks to game with on a
regular basis? Come learn about the MISFITS of Gaming club and other
groups in the area.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rachel Kronick, Dave Rust</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Comics Through Their Ages</strong><br/>What
defines the Golden Age of Comics? What about the Silver Age? What age
are we in now? Perhaps the lines between the ages are a little more
blurred than you think...<br/><font size="-1"><em>Roy C. Booth, <strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, Jonathan Palmer, Dan Wallace, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Anime: An Industry on the Brink</strong><br/>With
the fall of Geneon and proliferation of fan-subs, the future of Anime
as a viable commercial medium may be jeopardy. What steps must the
industry take to remain successful? How can loyal Otaku do their part
to keep Anime alive and well?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Scott K. Jamison, Brian Jonas, Jo Thomsen, Matt Weinberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Sci-Fi and Fantasy Essentials</strong><br/>Let's
see if we can come up with a top ten list for "must-read" sci-fi books
and another top ten list for fantasy novels. What are the Foundations
to become a literate sci-fi geek?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Bob Alberti, Windy Bowlsby, Rob Johnson, Adam Stemple, Jody Wurl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Current State of A.I.</strong><br/>How
far off is SkyNet? Do we need to start worrying about the Internets
taking over? What are some positive advances in artificial intelligence
development?<br/><font size="-1"><em>William Crolley, Aaron Vander Giessen</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Bollywood Sci-fi</strong><br/>What's coming out of India that has a distinct sci-fi or fantasy flavor?<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Kenneth Hite</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>I Miss You Cupcake!</strong><br/>Do
you miss Invader Zim? Does your love of Gir know no bounds? Bask in the
bacon-covered love of this series cancelled before its time.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Lori Fischer, Marie Hulslander, Tracie Peters, Michael Scott Shappe</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Chick Flicks: A Confessional</strong><br/>Two
(or more) men, typically identified as fans of John Wayne and Bruce
Lee, admit to their favorite movies and performers among so-called
"women's pictures:" screwball/romantic comedies, musicals, suspense,
soap operas: Bette Davis, Joan Crawford, Lana Turner, Elizabeth Taylor,
Meg Ryan, Julia Roberts, etc.<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Christenson, Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Kelly McCullough Reading</strong><br/>Join Kelly McCullough for a reading from one of his works.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Kelly McCullough</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">P1<br/>Arts</td><td valign="top"><strong>Iron Artist</strong><br/>Come
watch as our very own Iron Artists battle to bring life to the Secret
Ingredient. They will be given a scene and an hour in which to bring
life to their creation, engaging in a frenzied battle to win the
people's acclaim forever. Who's art scene will reign supreme?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Louis Frank, Kelvin Hatle, Eryn Hildebrand, ASL Interpreter, Christopher Jones, Melissa Kaercher, Perrin Klumpp, <strong>John Kovalic</strong>, Jennifer Menken, Amanda Shuckman, Gordon Smuder, Video Team, Matt Waterhouse</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 11:00am - 12:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/Andrew &amp; David</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, <strong>David Weber</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Thrown a Controller or Manual Across the Room Lately?</strong><br/>What's
happened to your favorite game series, franchise, or genre? Has it
gotten to the point where you don't even want to pick up a D20 or
controller anymore? Are there series that have constantly improved over
time?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Shawn Brandvold, Sarah Hertz, Stephan Stomberg</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Material Adaptation</strong><br/>What's
the writing process like for adapting material from one medium (like a
movie script) to another (like a novel). What about using licensed
characters that someone else created?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Roy C. Booth, S.D. Hintz, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Are Social Subcultures in Fandom Still Relevant?</strong><br/>Fandom
has always had it's subcultures, but does fandom really represent the
multiculturalism we pride ourselves on? Is the 'melting pot' metaphor
applicable to fandom? Has tolerance and understanding of minorities
truly migrated to fandom? If so, are social subcultures like feminist,
gay, disabled, and other minority fandom cultures still relevant? New
ideas and technologies have migrated from SF into society, but are
minorities truly represented in "main-stream" SF&amp;F?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Joe Agee, Andrew Berthke, Don Kaiser, Rachel Kronick, Jen Manna, Claudia Slovacek</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Subverting Tropes</strong><br/>Discuss the basic tropes of SF/F/H and how to subvert, twisted, and otherwise stand them on their ear.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Rob Callahan, Damian Sheridan, Adam Stemple, Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Weaponry of Star Trek</strong><br/>From
assault phasers to quantum torpedoes, disrupters to anti-matter
charges, discuss the many weapons and defenses of Star Trek and
determine their real-world feasibility.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Beitscher, Seth Chmelik, <strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, George Richard</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Bloom<br/>Movies</td><td valign="top"><strong>Star Wars with Peter Mayhew</strong><br/>Join us for an informative Q&amp;A with Peter Mayhew.<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Peter Mayhew</strong>, Video Team</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>The Venture Bros.</strong><br/>How
can one single animated series be so awesome? Discuss before the
Monarch brings furious anger down upon you! Maybe we'll even figure out
all the hidden secrets of Dr. Girlfriend while we're at it.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Chris Pasquarette, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Gold Knight: The Lives of Iron Man</strong><br/>Since
getting hit by shrapnel in Viet Nam in 1962, billionaire
industrialist-inventor Anthony Stark has built innumerable suits of
Iron Man armor, helped found the Avengers, palled around with a Thunder
God, dated every Marvel woman except May Parker, struggled with
alcoholism, been possessed by Kang the Conqueror, died about three
times, been replaced in the suit by best friend Rhodey and an alternate
universe teen version of himself, replaced Rummy as Secretary of
Defense, lead the winning side in Marvel's super hero Civil War, and
now serves as Director of Shield. Something about Tony Stark makes him
continue to fascinate through brilliant story arcs and ludicrous ones.
Let's talk about who, what, where, when, and why.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman, Jonathan Palmer</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Geeks Read Panel</strong><br/>Join
the MISFITS club Geeks Read for our monthly book discussion. Learn
about this fun sci-fi/fantasy book club and how you can join and get
involved.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jodie Gustafson, Alicia Lemunion</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 12:30pm - 1:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Larry &amp; Mercedes</strong><br/>Signing/autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Everything Old is New Again</strong><br/>Nintendo's
Virtual Console service, Playstation Network, Xbox Live, and other
emulators have created a great interest in retro video games. What are
your favorites and how do you take your retro-interest to the next
level with constructing MAME consoles?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Nessa Fedde, Jesse Richardson, Tim Wilsie</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>Women and Comic Books</strong><br/>Yes
we read them! Why don't the comic companies realize that they write for
an audience that includes women? Come discuss your favorite comics,
characters, and creators and what needs to be done in the industry to
help execs realize the market niche they're missing.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Cynthia Booth, Alexandra Howes, Melissa Kaercher</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>At-Con Post Mortem</strong><br/>So,
how did you like year ten of the con? Tell the folks in charge - the
good, the bad, and the ugly. (Hopefully it's mostly good!) Come and
meet the new Events Division director as well!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Windy Bowlsby, Christopher Jones, Perrin Klumpp, Michael Lee, Jeremy Stomberg, Pat Wick, Tim Wick, Ishmael Williams</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Books You've Thrown Across the Room!</strong><br/>The title says it all.  What has made you chuck a book across a room?  Watch out for flying literature!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Mariah Fryer, Jenni Klumpp</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Mythbusting!</strong><br/>Mythbusters
has a hardcore geek/science audience. From their movie-themed James
Bond and Superhero specials to busting urban myths, what do you like
about the show and what are some myths you'd like them to take a crack
at?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Romeo Azar, Jay Curry</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>Doctor Who by Decade: The Nineties</strong><br/>Covering
the 1990's era Dr. Who, this is the fourth in a series of four panels
exploring the rich and varied history of the classic British
science-fiction series, focusing on the expanded universe (audios,
books, comics) and the 1996 McGann TV Movie.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Heidi Johnson, Lars Pearson, Michael D. Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Specters, Shades and Ectoplasm</strong><br/>The
ghost story is a classic tale that never seems to die out. What's the
nature of the appeal of a good spooky tale about the restless dead?
What do hauntings say about us? Let's talk about the good, the bad and
the ugly portrayals of ghosts in genre fiction.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jerrod Balzer, S.D. Hintz, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, Catherine Lundoff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">LL<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Karl Wolff Reading</strong><br/>Join Karl Wolff for a reading from one of his works.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Karl Wolff</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 2:00pm - 3:00pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/Dr. Jim &amp; Greg</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A2<br/>Gaming</td><td valign="top"><strong>Are You Ready to Rock?</strong><br/>Rhythm-based
games like Guitar Hero, Rock Band, Elite Beat Agents, and others have
become very popular in the last few years. Is there still room for
classics like DDR? Where do you see this trend going in the future and
is there any crossover with wanting to learn real-life instruments?<br/><font size="-1"><em>Matt Everhart, Mariah Fryer, Clay Lamkin</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A3<br/>Comics</td><td valign="top"><strong>DC and Marvel Updates</strong><br/>Been
away from comics for a while? Come and find out what's been going on in
the DC and Marvel universes. How are your favorite characters faring?
The first half of the hour is devoted to DC and the second half to
Marvel.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Michael Lee, Jonathan Palmer, Dan Wallace</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A4<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Making The "Year-Round" Convention a Reality</strong><br/>The parent organization behind CONvergence also runs many other  
events and clubs year-round under the banner of MISFITS, including  
Trivia Contests, Scavenger Hunts, and Geek Proms. The fun doesn't  
have to stop on Sunday, you know!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Dave Benhart, Jodie Gustafson, Elliott James, Thomas Keeley, Peter Verrant</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A6<br/>Lit</td><td valign="top"><strong>Meet a Librarian!</strong><br/>We've
managed to round up a few librarians to answer your questions about the
profession. What's the day-to-day grind like? If you are interested in
becoming a librarian or just learning about the occupation, this panel
is for you!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Jenni Klumpp, Rebecca Marjesdatter, Kevin McIntyre, Hilary Moon Murphy, Greg Prickman, Lynne Thomas</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">A7<br/>Science</td><td valign="top"><strong>Ultimate Home Theatre</strong><br/>Want
to start investing in and constructing a future-proof home
entertainment center? What equipment is a must, what will be outdated
shortly, and what can't you live without? If you want to learn to tell
your 1080P's from your Progressive Scans, this is the place to start.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Hank Lederer, Drew Youngdahl</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Edina<br/>TV</td><td valign="top"><strong>TV Shows on DVD: Season Seven</strong><br/>Join
us for our annual review of the best and worst of TV Shows on Shiny
Disc. We're now in our seventh year (on the 'air' as long as Next Gen
and DS9, whoo!) Will our panel become 'TV Shows on Blu-Ray' next year?
Signs point to yes!<br/><font size="-1"><em>David Margosian, Matt Savelkoul, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Lizards, Reptiles, and Amphibians in Fact, Folklore, Fiction, and Film</strong><br/>We
continue our series of Bio-Horror panels about scary critters
(previously we've surveyed bats, bees &amp; wasps, apes, ants, and
spiders). This time we'll consider both little criters such as frogs
and toads as well as big critters both real (T-Rex) and surreal
(Gojirah!)<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman, Melissa Kaercher</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 3:30pm - 4:30pm</td><td valign="top">Sign<br/>Auto</td><td valign="top"><strong>Signing w/ Marv, Bernie,  &amp; Len</strong><br/>Signing/Autographing<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 5:00pm - 6:00pm</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Closing Ceremonies</strong><br/>Closing Ceremonies<br/><font size="-1"><em><strong>Trace Beaulieu</strong>, Windy Bowlsby, <strong>Christian Colquhoun</strong>, <strong>Larry Dixon</strong>, <strong>Daren Dochterman</strong>, <strong>Mark Evanier</strong>, <strong>Kenneth Hite</strong>, ASL Interpreter, Christopher Jones, <strong>Dr. Jim Kakalios</strong>, Perrin Klumpp, <strong>Harry Knowles</strong>, <strong>Jay Knowles</strong>, <strong>John Kovalic</strong>, <strong>Mercedes Lackey</strong>, <strong>Bridget Landry</strong>, Michael Lee, <strong>Peter Mayhew</strong>, <strong>Robert Meyer Burnett</strong>, <strong>Andrew Probert</strong>, Jeremy Stomberg, Video Team, <strong>Vincent Truitner</strong>, <strong>David Weber</strong>, <strong>Len Wein</strong>, <strong>Greg Weisman</strong>, Pat Wick, Tim Wick, Ishmael Williams, <strong>Wally Wingert</strong>, <strong>Marv Wolfman</strong>, <strong>Bernie Wrightson</strong></em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Sun 7:30pm - 1:30am</td><td valign="top">Kr<br/>HotDish</td><td valign="top"><strong>Diversicon Party</strong><br/>Hang
out with some volunteers for this multicultural, multimedia speculative
fiction convention, the 16th edition of which will be held August 1-3
in the Holiday Inn Metrodome. Party goes from 7:30 pm until 1:30 am.<br/><font size="-1"><em>Eric M. Heideman</em></font></td></tr>
    <tr>
<td valign="top" width="75">Mon 12:00am - 1:00am</td><td valign="top">MnStg<br/>MainStg</td><td valign="top"><strong>Michael Sheard Five Day Memorial Panel</strong><br/>To
end our convention we remember and celebrate the lives of all of our
friends who have left us over the last ten years. And yes, the timing
of this panel makes the con officially 5 DAYS!<br/><font size="-1"><em>Anton Petersen, Video Team, Tim Wick</em></font></td></tr>
</tbody></table>

